Have you ever thought about
why Guo Zijian, of all people, was assigned to
the Red 1st Battalion of our 396th Brigade
as the battalion commander?
I don't even need to think about it.
Know what?
He made a mistake and was sent here for punishment.
You're just speaking out of anger.
Our Red 1st Battalion
is the flagship of the group army.
Sent to an honors battalion for punishment?
Then you tell me why.
Let me tell you the truth.
It was Deputy Corps Commander Liang's idea.
Deputy Corps Commander Liang?
Guo Zijian,
although he acts a little out of line,
some of his ideas regarding army reform,
and even his intentions,
suit Deputy Corps Commander Liang's taste.
I think Xu Lingjun is watching him too.
I think it won't be long before
he's transferred to Group Army Training.
I get it now.
This kid is just here to pad his resume!
Pad his resume?
Given his performance these past 3 months,
alienating everyone around him,
do you think he's padding his resume?
Not to mention,
after he arrived at the 1st Battalion,
how much it has changed
is obvious to everyone.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Tell you what?
About Deputy Corps Commander Liang.
Deputy Corps Commander Liang ordered us
not to give him any special treatment.
He just wanted to see
exactly how capable he is.
The reason I'm telling you now
is that I hope you can
look at the big picture
and be more objective
when dealing with Guo Zijian.
Objective,
or polite?
Objective, of course.
The thing is,
he might suit the commander's taste,
but he doesn't suit mine.
Old Suo, I'll say it again.
You must keep that quick temper of yours
under control.
Let me tell you,
I shudder every time I think about it.
I always worry something will go wrong.
Don't forget,
you are at a critical stage right now.
Why do I feel like
this isn't the commander testing him?
This is him testing me!
I've noticed
that our great Political Commissar Kang's
ideological work
has gone up a notch.
I was just confused.
Guo Zijian
Staff Officer Liang
Battalion Commander Guo
Yes?
Is there something else?
I just wanted to thank you.
Thank me for what?
For supporting the First Battalion.
I wasn't supporting the First Battalion.
I was just sticking to the facts.
Alright.
Then thank you for your fairness.
You're welcome. It's my duty.
Could I get your contact info?
Let's keep in touch.
Goodbye.
What's going on?
What do you mean, what's going on?
That Staff Officer Liang...
...is a rare talent.
Let's keep in touch.
Speak.
Why so serious?
I'm your sister, not one of your soldiers.
If you have nothing else, I'm hanging up.
Wait, I do! I have something.
Bro.
You haven't taken your annual leave yet?
My graduation ceremony is in half a month.
Can you come back for it?
Mom and Dad will be there.
Do I really need to go?
How can they compare to you?
No one can take
my brother's place in my heart.
Bro.
It's the most important moment of my life.
I'll be heartbroken if you don't come.
How about this?
I'll tell Chen Hanxiao not to come,
and make room for you.
All right, all right.
Don't give me that.
So are you coming or not?
I have an assignment coming up.
We'll see when the time comes. Gotta go.
What?
Girlfriend?
What girlfriend?
Mind your own business.
Since you have a girlfriend,
when dealing with other female comrades,
you must keep your distance.
We are a disciplined force.
You must be loyal in your relationships.
You're overthinking this.
I just made one phone call,
and you've already figured out
which kindergarten my kids will go to?
Of course.
Our military kindergarten
is really quite good.
Your sister-in-law is currently...
Okay, okay, okay. That's enough.
One, two, three, four!
Five kilometers!
Oh, how I love you!
Skip a single day,
And I miss you to death!
Brothers over there!
Push harder!
Did you hear?
Our commander is getting transferred.
What?
Stop talking nonsense.
That's impossible.
Why is it impossible?
He came here as the acting commander.
Do you know what "acting" means?
It means it's temporary.
No, where did you hear this nonsense?
Don't worry about where I heard it.
Everyone's talking about it anyway.
He was chosen by Group Army Training.
He's just using us as a stepping stone.
No way.
The Group Army's tactical exercise...
...is about to begin.
He just got us the main assault role.
He wouldn't abandon us now.
Stop spreading these rumors.
Why are you getting mad at me?
I'm upset about it too.
Well, I don't believe it.
Our commander definitely wouldn't do that.
Yeah, Squad Leader.
I don't think he'd do that either.
But what he wants is one thing.
If the Group Army insists on moving him,
what can he do?
Keep quiet. Nobody will think you're mute.
Look.
No way.
I'm going to find Lao Sun and Lao Gao now.
We'll petition our superiors together.
We have to keep our commander here.
Company Commander!
Why aren't you guys organizing training?
Where are you headed?
Commander, you can't leave.
Right, you can't leave.
Who said I'm leaving?
See, I told you it was just a rumor.
It's your fault, you and your big mouth.
As for our commander, the group army...
...does have a new appointment in mind.
But exactly what kind of appointment...
...hasn't been officially issued yet.
So until then...
...stop making wild guesses.
Especially...
...don't pull stunts like this petition.
Do you hear me?
But...
...we still have to voice our opinions.
If the transfer order comes down...
...won't it be too late?
Li Songwei.
You used to want me gone more than anyone.
What, now you can't bear to see me leave?
I can't bear it. So what?
It's not just me...
...everyone hates to see you go, right?
Right, exactly! Commander!
Commander, we don't want you to leave.
Before the higher-ups assign my new job...
...they'll definitely ask for my opinion.
Since everyone wants me to stay...
...even if I have to throw a tantrum...
...I'll firmly refuse to leave.
You said it yourself.
Don't you fool us.
All right.
Stop being so mushy.
The group army's combat drill starts soon.
Our First Battalion is the main assault.
Put more of your focus...
...into training.
We must prove to everyone in this exercise
...that we're still the Red Army Battalion.
Yes, sir!
Head back, all of you.
And prepare well for training.
What did Deputy Commander Liang tell you?
Just one thing.
Await instructions.
How's the repair going?
It's done.
Good. Go get some rest.
Yes, Commander.
Commander,
What is it?
I...
Didn't Li Songwei pass on the message?
Are you here to persuade me too?
No, Commander.
I wanted to say,
don't take Commander Li's words to heart.
If
you really want to go to Operations,
then you should go.
Come on up.
Have a seat.
Commander,
honestly, Operations and Training
is a really good place.
After all, it's a headquarters unit,
not as grueling as our grassroots units.
Besides,
there's more room for promotion.
For you personally,
it really is a better choice.
Commander,
you've done enough for our 1st Battalion.
Really.
You've made the 1st Battalion
change so much.
But we
can't act like unweaned children,
relying on you for everything.
And we certainly can't
hold you back.
With you saying that,
I didn't come to the 1st Battalion
and serve as its commander in vain.
By the way, Commander.
I want to give you this.
A Type 99A.
This must have taken a lot of work.
You're just giving it to me?
Willing to part with it?
I am.
Commander,
last time,
that book you gave me about exoskeletons,
I read it too.
If I get the chance,
I'd like to try it out.
I'll start with a model first.
Once I've learned everything I need,
I'll make a real suit for you.
Wow.
Making that thing isn't easy.
Besides needing the knowledge,
you also need funding.
Commander,
do you know
the most important thing I've learned
from you?
It wouldn't be arrogance, would it?
Of course not, Commander.
Really,
what I learned from you is that
as long as you dare to dream and act,
your goals
can be achieved.
Hesitating and overthinking
will only keep you standing still.
Good job, Wu Dongsheng.
Capable in both theory and practice,
you truly are our top soldier.
Thank you for the gift.
I'll take good care of it.
Guo Zijian.
What?
Are you here to learn from me,
or to fulfill our bet?
I'm not interested in your crooked tricks.
I need to talk to you.
I heard
you're moving to Group Army Training.
If that's the case,
why do you insist on going against me?
Even if your battalion leads the attack,
changing commanders right before battle...
don't you think it will affect the drill?
Jiang Shengqiang.
Whatever the organization plans for me,
while I'm still with the 1st Battalion,
I will lead it well.
Also,
the First Battalion's current success
is not just thanks to me, Guo Zijian.
Even if I leave right this second,
I believe the First Battalion
can still do well in the drill.
And let me correct you on one thing.
I never wanted to
go against you.
You didn't get the main attack role
because you lack the capability.
Guo Zijian!
Comrades,
we just received combat orders from above.
The troops will move out immediately.
For so many years,
our Red First Battalion,
despite being an honors battalion
and a traditional Red Army unit,
has, however,
for a long time
failed to be
a solid benchmark military battalion.
But this time,
we are different.
We will carry this glory,
this honor,
and this readiness for combat
as we head to the frontlines of the drill.
Before we set off,
I have an urgent announcement to make.
After repeated deliberation
by the higher command,
as of today,
Comrade Guo Zijian's appointment is here.
Comrade Guo Zijian
is officially our Battalion Commander.
Now,
let's welcome Commander Guo
to address everyone
and say a few words.
Location
Training Ground
Objective
Victory
Battalion, attention!
fix bayonets!
Move out!
Yes, sir!
Currently,
a portion of the Blue Army's forces
is advancing toward Yuhuang Peak.
Yuhuang Peak
has always been the high ground
fiercely contested in past exercises.
Whoever takes Yuhuang Peak
will secure the most advantageous
offensive position in this battle.
The Blue Army wants to strike first,
but this tactic
seems to lack a bit of originality.
Exactly.
Reconnaissance shows
that the troops sent to Yuhuang Peak
are not their main force.
The Blue Army's command post
and its main force
should be in Xifeng Valley.
Therefore,
this is their decoy strategy.
Their objective
is to lure our troops to Yuhuang Peak,
and then from Xifeng Valley,
target our command post
with a direct strike.
I will now announce the battle plan.
Tomorrow morning at 0700 hours,
the first shot
will be fired by the 1st Battalion.
Guo Zijian!
Sir!
Your mission is very clear.
Target the Blue Army's command post
and hit them hard!
Yes, sir!
2nd Battalion!
Sir!
You'll support the 1st Battalion.
Yes, sir!
3rd Battalion!
Sir!
After the fire strike on the Blue Army,
encircle them
and wipe out their effective forces.
Yes, sir!
4th Battalion!
Sir!
Keep a close watch
on the Blue Army's Yuhuang Peak garrison.
Stop them coordinating with Xifeng Valley
and returning to reinforce it.
Yes, sir!
Everyone,
this is our
last assembly before the battle.
I expect that,
assuming there are no major changes,
once I issue the combat order,
you will all,
without fail,
resolutely execute it.
Comrades,
though the 404th Brigade is tough,
I believe victory goes to a united force.
As long as our 396th Brigade
unites as one and fights bravely,
we will definitely create a miracle.
We will accomplish the mission!
Hurry up and get ready.
Battalion Commander Guo,
this
was provided by the Group Army's Recon Battalion
as the main assault's strike target.
Thank you, Chief of Staff.
Commander,
judging by the deployment here,
the Group Army's
recon intel given to our recon battalion
is accurate.
This is their command post.
Hold on.
Keep watching.
Commander!
The Blue Force recon unit is approaching!
Fall back!
Move.
Check up ahead.
Keep up.
I thought we were spotted.
Luckily, it was just a recon squad leader.
He's no ordinary squad leader.
You know him?
He was one of my recruits.
From when you were a recruit squad leader?
Company Commander Li,
don't underestimate him.
He's an all-army competition champion.
He's no rookie.
Even so, he's just...
all brawn and no brains.
Shut up.
Continue.
That guy is Yang Maolin.
The recon squad leader from just now.
I trained him, I know him.
An elite scout like him
wouldn't miss a single clue.
He clearly saw it,
but chose to ignore it.
It was too deliberate.
Exactly.
This command post
is most likely a decoy.
Commander.
You're here so early.
You should've rested before coming.
It's better to be fully rested
to observe the enemy lines
and direct the battle.
I've got plenty of energy.
This Long Yuanshan,
truly is an expert of the Blue Force.
Judging from his pre-exercise deployment,
there are traps within traps.
Very impressive.
Haven't you said this before?
Throughout history,
the most brilliant tactic in war
is also the most common.
That is, in the back-and-forth,
mixing truth with deception.
That's what makes a battle interesting.
Right.
If the battle isn't intense,
the troops won't get solid training.
And the officers
won't be pushed to their limits.
You're absolutely right, Commander.
Give me a prediction.
In this exercise,
what are the Red Force's chances?
Me?
In my opinion...
I'll give it to you straight, then.
Were you going to lie to me?
Of course you'll give it straight.
Yes, sir.
I feel that
the higher-ups
arranging for Comrade Suo Jian'an
to assume command as acting head
surely had their own reasoning.
But I think
regarding Comrade Suo Jian'an's boldness,
he's a bit
overly steady
and lacking in drive.
Moreover,
his chief of staff is newly appointed.
They'll have shortcomings in command.
Therefore,
my assessment is
the Red Force is in danger.
Isn't Guo Zijian your favorite officer?
Don't even mention him.
Commander,
I lost an operations officer for nothing.
Look at you getting all worked up.
What's there to be worked up about?
Don't you think Guo Zijian
is more suited to be a grassroots commander?
Though he wasn't assigned to Operations,
still,
for discovering his potential,
you deserve a lot of credit.
I wouldn't dare claim that credit.
Commander, without your nod,
with Guo Zijian's stubborn temper,
he would never have made it
into the ranks of our 8th Group Army.
You've got quite a strong sense of honor.
Ling Jun,
this exercise...
my prediction is
it'll be worth watching.
Squad leader,
just now, you saw with your own eyes
how the Red team's reconnaissance squad
left.
Of course.
The one leading the Red team
is a veteran scout.
Plus,
they kept a trick up their sleeve.
The members of their squad
had been gone for quite a while
before their rear guard finally retreated.
Good thing
I slacked off a bit
and didn't stand up.
I almost became their prisoner.
They're pros.
Chief of Staff,
take a look.
Does our deployment here
still have any weak spots?
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo,
I took office right before this drill.
I'll defer to your judgment.
No need to be modest.
I actually know
you adapted to the role very quickly.
I just
did a bit of homework.
I still have a long way to go.
Based on the troop
and firepower deployment,
I haven't found any weak spots.
But regarding the frontline situation,
I still want
to go check it out in person.
All right.
Make it quick.
Yes, sir.
Brigade Commander.
Watch what you call me.
But right now, you
are the Red team's commander.
Besides,
Brigade Commander Yang is now
entirely focused on
this new research project.
From the looks of it,
he'll probably be transferred soon.
Furthermore,
before he joined the research team,
he personally recommended you
to be the acting Brigade Commander.
This shows
that he highly approves of you.
Besides,
the group army this time
arranged for you
to be the Red commander for this drill.
What does that show?
It shows that after Commander Yang leaves,
you becoming the Brigade Commander
is a sure thing!
What do you mean "a sure thing"?
While I am still the Deputy Commander,
we cannot break the rules.
Keep that in mind.
Fine, fine, fine.
Whatever you say.
It won't be long now, anyway.
How are the battalions deploying?
Right.
I'm here to report this to you.
Just now, when the commissar and I
went to each battalion
to inspect the troop deployments,
we found that Guo Zijian was missing.
Guo Zijian is missing?
The battle is about to start!
He's a battalion commander,
yet he abandons his post!
Where did he go?
We don't know.
But the sentry said
he took 1st Company Commander Li Songwei
to inspect the troops.
But as for where exactly they went,
he couldn't give a clear answer.
He was clearly trying to fool us.
Guo Zijian...
Whenever you mention his name,
my eyelid twitches non-stop.
I originally thought
that before the exercise,
we could send this troublemaker packing.
But I didn't expect
Deputy Commander Liang to change his mind.
No matter what,
after the exercise is over,
I think
we need to grill his ass.
He's completely out of line.
Where is the commissar?
The commissar told me to come back first
to discuss the battle deployment with you.
He's still at the 1st Battalion.
Sang Haitian,
tell me the truth.
Where exactly did Guo Zijian go?
You're the instructor,
he's the battalion commander.
There's nothing to hide.
Commissar,
you're hiding a knife behind that smile.
Calm down first, okay?
You are
the brigade party secretary,
and I'm the battalion party secretary.
In front of you,
I'd never dare lie to you.
Right?
Then why isn't he at any of the positions?
Speak.
Commissar,
I think
you also know Comrade Guo Zijian well.
Actually, he's a simple guy.
Just a bit single-minded.
All he thinks about is fighting.
And how to win battles.
Honestly, our country and our people
need soldiers like him.
Our troops
also need officers like him.
I think he's pretty good.
Sang Haitian,
can you come up with some new lines?
I did.
I told him,
he must save his strength for the battle.
But he just wouldn't listen.
He insists on doing everything himself.
I guess right now
he's off checking the roads again.
Checking the roads isn't something
that can be done in a day.
Sang Haitian,
your acting has really improved.
I wouldn't dare act in front of you.
Speak. Come on, tell me.
Continue.
I assure you, he'll be here right away.
Report!
Speak.
Chief,
we've contacted the battalion commander.
Where is he?
The commander...
Spit it out!
The commissar is here.
What can't you say?
Tell the truth.
He said he'll be here right away.
Right away?
Right away.
Good, Sang Haitian.
Tell me,
all night long,
how many times have you said "right away"?
My fingers
and toes
added up
aren't enough to count them!
Commissar,
when I say "right away" this time,
he really will be here right away.
Fine.
Then I'll believe you one more time.
Commissar,
a big battle is coming.
You must save your strength.
You've walked over ten thousand steps.
Have a seat.
You really won't sit?
Our commander specifically told us
to make sure you two eat and drink well.
See
if there's anything else you need.
We only need to see your commander.
Our battalion commander,
I really don't know where he is.
Xiao Fang.
Here.
These two comrades from directing
want to see our battalion commander.
You talk to them.
Well, you two,
I'll get back to work.
Enjoy your meal.
Our battalion commander isn't available.
Then we'll see the political instructor.
Or the battalion staff officer.
We'll see whoever is available.
Reporting, sir.
They...
are all unavailable.
You...
It's fine.
Well, since that's the case,
we'll just start our work ourselves.
Let's go.
You can't do that.
Without orders from above,
you can't wander around.
We aren't wandering around.
We're from the directing group.
We're authorized to inspect everywhere.
Everywhere?
Men and women have boundaries, you know.
How can you say you'll inspect everywhere?
What are you talking about?
Anyway, it's just not allowed.
Squad Leader Hong.
Here.
Please take note.
Yes, sir.
Red Force, Battalion 1
is obstructing the directing team's work,
preventing us from obtaining
regular exercise information.
Therefore, points will be deducted.
Yes, sir.
Don't write nonsense!
Now, can we begin our work?
Staff Officer Liang, Squad Leader Hong.
Have you eaten?
Battalion Commander Guo.
Your First Battalion sure puts on airs.
Not only did you block us from the chief,
you also obstructed our normal work.
Did that really happen?
How could you treat
two directing team comrades like this?
You're asking for it, kid.
Aren't you?
Remember this from now on.
To these two beautiful directing officers,
you must be polite.
And you must show respect.
Understood?
Yes, Battalion Commander!
He's a recruit, he doesn't know better.
That's no big deal.
But Battalion Commander Guo,
if you have any combat operations
or deployments,
you absolutely must not hide them from us.
Otherwise, if the records are incomplete,
and you lose points after the exercise,
it will be hard to explain.
What operations could there be?
I'm just going to check on the companies.
You've been working so hard.
Don't you want to rest a bit more?
No need.
We'll start working right now.
So dedicated.
Please.
Thanks for your hard work.
Battalion Commander.
The Commissar is still waiting for you.
Got it.
Good job.
I'll reward you later.
You taught me well, Commander.
Staff Officer Liang, Staff Officer Liang!
You really surprised me today.
How so?
Give this to me.
Squad Leader Hong.
Please record this.
Red's 1st Battalion obstructed our work,
preventing us from getting normal intel.
Mark it as a point deduction.
That was a good bluff.
I almost actually recorded it.
I wasn't bluffing.
Wait, no.
You really want to record it?
I'm acting according to regulations.
Is there a problem?
N-No.
I thought you...
had loosened up.
By the way, Staff Officer Liang.
Go ahead.
We were just doing our normal jobs.
Why did they stop us?
Could they really be up to something?
You've finally grasped the main point.
So what do we do?
Just one thing:
Keep a close eye.
Does that mean we're in for a good show?
Staff Officer Liang.
Tiejun.
This time
is our first showdown with Suo Jian'an.
Did you know?
This Suo Jian'an,
before the military reform,
was the military region's theory model.
But I just don't know
how much real ability he has.
I heard
that 396th Brigade's Commander Yang
is executing a special mission this time.
He was supposed to take leave to command,
but the higher-ups flat-out denied it.
I reckon
the commanders want to use this exercise
to test Suo Jian'an's mettle,
to see if he
is really cut out to be a chief commander.
So you see,
the firepower assigned to him
and all elements are well in place.
He even got the group army's recon unit.
You could really say
he has a strong and well-equipped force.
So that means,
Suo Jian'an is going all out this time
to have a major showdown with us.
What a pity.
Yehuling
is destined to be the place of his defeat.
Brigade Commander,
this is Suo Jian'an's path to promotion.
Don't you think we should...
slightly,
I mean, just slightly,
save him a tiny bit of face?
Let's not make his loss look too ugly.
Nonsense!
On the battlefield, there are only rivals.
There's no room for favors.
Why was the Blue Force established?
It's for us, the Blue Force,
to be the whetstone for the Red Force,
to improve their combat effectiveness.
If we care about face and show mercy,
then we are incompetent.
So this time,
not only must we fight,
but give 120 percent of our strength
to fight him.
If Suo Jian'an actually wins,
it proves he has the skills
to be a good brigade commander.
If he isn't up to it,
then I'm sorry,
we'll just have to offer him up
as a sacrifice to the 404th Brigade.
I was just kidding.
The basic situation
is like this.
Let me ask you one more thing.
The Xifeng Valley command post is a fake.
Are you sure about that?
Commissar,
I used to be a recon company commander.
These little tricks can't fool me.
Haitian.
Yes, sir!
The situation is urgent.
I'm immediately taking
Zijian back to the command center
to quickly study
the combat plan in depth.
Until you receive new combat deployments,
you are responsible for supervising
all combat units under the battalion
to follow the original plan
and prepare for battle.
I guarantee mission completion!
Officer Ma.
Yes, sir!
Notify Deputy Commander Suo immediately.
Ask the Army Recon Battalion to get ready.
Yes, sir!
You may have merits this time,
but next time
you act on your own,
expect to be disciplined.
Yes, sir.
I will absolutely obey orders.
Understood.
Brigade Commander,
The patrol squad reports
they found traces of Red Force recon.
They must have come to double-check
the location of our command post.
I didn't expect Suo Jian'an
to act so cautiously.
You didn't alert them, did you?
Everything went according to plan.
They suspect nothing.
Good.
Order the camouflage unit at Xifeng Valley
to relocate immediately.
Yes, sir.
It's fake.
Look, Guo Zijian.
You leave your post without permission,
act on your own,
just to reach this wild conclusion?
Deputy Brigade Commander,
it's not a wild conclusion.
Please trust my judgment.
My analysis is based on facts.
Your so-called facts
are just that their scouts
didn't spot you.
That can only be called intuition.
Intuition isn't fact.
Am I supposed to rely on your intuition
to conclude that
the Army Group's Recon Battalion
found a fake Blue Force command post?
Zeng Muhan!
Here!
Come in.
Yes, sir.
Comrade Zeng Muhan,
Commander Guo Zijian of the 1st Battalion
conducted a field recon.
As for your preliminary recon
and the conclusion you reached,
he has raised doubts.
Tell us about your recon findings.
Yes, sir.
Squad leader.
The troops have moved out.
When are we pulling out?
What's the rush?
They haven't given us the signal yet.
When we leave in a bit,
I'll head to Huangshi Ridge.
You head to Tiger Pass.
Squad leader,
why split into two groups?
A diversion tactic?
Stop asking questions.
Reporting, sir.
Our reconnaissance report
is derived from multiple recon methods
and synthesized comprehensively.
It is backed by a massive amount of data.
Look here.
Points A, B, and C.
These are typical command post setups.
Moreover, the command post's location,
as well as the patrol and security units'
forward positions,
all fully prove
this is the Blue Force's command post.
Not only that.
The supporting facilities
and logistics units
all match the textbook requirements
perfectly.
However, there are two
obvious problems.
First,
all personnel at the command post
are systematically
performing certain actions and routines.
Second,
the opposite hill
is an excellent observation point.
I've seen the footage of your operation.
When you were doing recon,
you chose this exact spot.
According to command post
setup principles,
such an observation point
would never be left for the enemy.
Makes sense.
On the contrary.
This observation point's
actual distance to the valley
has exceeded the security perimeter
by command post setup principles.
Besides,
their patrol team
also passed through here.
This exactly proves
that to enhance security,
they even expanded their patrol radius.
If this command post were fake,
there would be no need for that.
That is exactly what makes me suspicious.
We have already crossed paths with
their patrol team.
They acted very undisciplined,
and even
seemed to let us go on purpose.
So I believe
all of this
is an illusion they deliberately set up.
Commander Guo,
your analysis
is based purely on on-site recon.
But relying solely on on-site recon
makes such judgments
too subjective,
lacking objective data support.
I believe
our analytical methods
are more comprehensive
and integrated.
Most importantly,
they are more scientific.
If we rely solely on data analysis,
it could just be typical
armchair strategy.
Watch your tone.
So theirs is armchair strategy,
but your conclusion is perfectly accurate?
Don't speak with such certainty.
Data evidence.
On-site recon.
Staff Officer Liang,
I actually think both of them
make a lot of sense.
If I were the commander,
I wouldn't know who to listen to.
Who do you support?
Eyes can deceive,
but data doesn't.
So you're saying Guo Zijian is wrong?
We're just here to record.
Don't judge right or wrong.
Battalion Commander Guo,
the battle is about to begin.
The brigade's entire combat deployment,
must it, because of your personal
guesswork,
be completely reshuffled?
Guesswork?
You think this is my personal guesswork?
This is the exact same principle
using Li Songwei to trick Jiang Shengqiang
when fighting the 2nd Battalion.
I can smell what they're up to.
No matter what you say,
without data to support it,
isn't it just subjective speculation?
If that's not guesswork, what is?
If we blindly
launch a strike,
what we expose
is not just our strategic intent,
but also our reckless command.
Commanders,
I know time is tight right now.
So,
please trust my judgment.
My graduation thesis's
main focus
was on the future army's
point-capture strike operations.
And as far as I know,
404th Brigade's Commander Long Yuanshan
had his postgraduate research
focused on this exact area.
All right, all right, enough.
We're in real combat now,
actual live-fire combat.
Why show off your theoretical research?
Exactly.
Even if you want to talk theory,
can you out-talk Deputy Commander Suo?
When Deputy Suo was a theory role model,
Commander Guo was still learning to shoot.
We're getting sidetracked.
Deputy Commander Suo,
I'm not trying to show off anything.
I just want to win this battle.
Even if we lose,
I don't want us to lose too badly.
What do you mean, "even if we lose"?
Let me tell you,
it's impossible for us to lose!
Who do you think you are?
The savior?
What do you think our leadership does?
Are we just good-for-nothings?
Idiots?
You think you're the only smart one?
Look how arrogant you are.
A top command student from the academy!
Old Suo, Old Suo.
Let's stick to the intel for now.
Nothing else.
The battle is imminent.
Let me tell you, Guo Zijian.
If it weren't for the Commissar,
I would relieve you of your command!
Deputy Commander,
if I've bruised your ego...